auctionstealer.com 2015-06-09

# AuctionStealer - Free online ebay auction sniper software free ebay sniper esnipe ebay snipe site e snipe auctions ebay auction sniper site bid sniper

TABLE OF CONTENTS

  * GENERAL OVERVIEW
  * INFORMATION WE COLLECT
  * INFORMATION USAGE
  * INFORMATION SECURITY
  * ACCESS, MODIFY OR DELETE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
  * PRIVACY DISPUTES
  * CONTACT INFORMATION

GENERAL OVERVIEW

AuctionStealer.com, Inc. created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on our login page. Privacy Policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date we post the revised Privacy Policy to the site, as well as to existing information held by us. 

By accepting the following terms, you consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the guidelines of our Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy is effective upon registration for new users, and is otherwise effective on April 12, 2012 for all users. The previous amendment to this Privacy Policy was effective for all users on May 15, 2008. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect personal information in order to provide you with a safe, customized, and efficient experience. This allows us to offer specialized features and services that may accommodate your unique circumstances. We only collect the necessary information for achieving this purpose. 

During the registration process, we ask you to provide us with Personally Identifiable information so we can identify you. This information includes your first name, last name, email address, auction username and auction password. Your auction username and auction password are required so that we can place bids on your behalf. 

When a user enters an auction item into our system, we store all details related to that item. This information is used to perform the service you have requested. After the auction ends, the information is retained for future review unless you specifically remove the item. 

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior in order to better understand our customers. This information may include the URL that you last visited, the URL you got to subsequently, your computer browser information, and your IP address. None of this information is tied to your personal information directly. 

"Cookies" are pieces of information that are passed to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to recognize repeat visitors, to automatically enter your login ID in our login form, and to provide additional features to make navigating our site easier and more efficient. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can turn them off using your browser's settings. Some of our business partners (e.g., tracking utility company) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.auctionstealer.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. 

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. 

INFORMATION USAGE

We use personal information in order to provide and enhance the services offered on our site. AuctionStealer.com, Inc. does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

We give you the ability to receive information via email about our Products and Services, updates to our site, and promotions that are targeted to your specific interest. If you do not opt-out of receiving these communications about our site, we will send them to you. 

From time to time, we might contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. You will have the opportunity opt-out of receiving these type of offers sent on behalf of third parties. You will also have the choice to respond to the offer or not. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information, such as your name and email address, is not transferred to the third party. 

We will send you service-related announcements on occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. 

At any time, you may change the communications you wish to receive or not, by updating your profile. In addition, in our emails and other communications, we will include instructions on how to unsubscribe and inform us of preferences if you decide you do not want to receive any future marketing or promotional emails from us. [See Access, Modify or Delete Your Personal Information] 

When placing a bid, on an auction item you have entered into our system, we send the auction site the item number, max bid, auction site username and auction site password. When available, we send this information using SSL encryption. No other information is transferred or disclosed. 

For your convenience, our site provides links to other sites. When you click on one of these links, you are leaving our site and entering another site. We are not responsible for such third party sites. You should carefully review the privacy statements of any other sites you visit, because those privacy statements will apply to your visit to such other sites. 

AuctionStealer.com, Inc. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with judicial or legal process served on AuctionStealer.com, Inc. or the site such as a court order or subpoena; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AuctionStealer.com, Inc., and that of our site; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AuctionStealer.com, Inc., its web sites, or the public. 

INFORMATION SECURITY

AuctionStealer.com, Inc. employs Industry standard protocols to help protect the confidentiality and integrity of personal information and to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of personal information. If you choose to contact AuctionStealer.com, Inc. through the site, you should be aware that any information transmitted electronically via the World Wide Web might not be 100% secure. AuctionStealer.com, Inc. assumes no liability for the loss of any information that you transmit to us via the World Wide Web. In communicating with you, we may send email as unencrypted plain text because we are aware that most Members, Guests, or Subscribers cannot readily process encrypted email. This is done for your convenience, but with the security concern that, if misrouted or intercepted, it could be read more easily than encrypted email. 

Should you choose to pay by credit card / electronic check when signing up for one of our premium services, you will be directed to one of our online merchants (PayPal or ClickBank). Once your transaction is completed, the only information the merchant shares back with AuctionStealer.com, Inc. is transactional information. AuctionStealer.com, Inc. does not receive financial information such as your credit card number. 

ACCESS, MODIFY OR DELETE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We endeavor to ensure that Personal Information is as accurate, complete, and current as necessary for the purposes for which we use that information. We encourage you to visit the Your Profile page, within the member section, to review your Personal Information. 

You can access your Personal Information on the Your Profile page, update it, correct it, or modify it as necessary. For example, you can change at any time your name, email address, or your preferences for receiving or not receiving emails. 

If you request that we cancel your account, you will not be able to use any of the services available to members on our site unless you re-register. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services [contact us](http://www.auctionstealer.com/contact.cfm). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

PRIVACY DISPUTES

AuctionStealer.com Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through this Web site, www.auctionstealer.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please [contact our privacy officer](http://www.auctionstealer.com/contact.cfm?privacy=yes). If you are not satisfied with our response you can [contact TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or concerns about (a) access to personal information, (b) the collection, use, management, or disclosure of personal information, (c) this policy or our information handling practices, or if you need further assistance with respect to our Privacy Policy, you may contact our Privacy Officer as indicated below. We will attempt to respond to your questions or concerns promptly after we receive them. 

E-mail: [Contact our Privacy Officer](http://www.auctionstealer.com/contact.cfm?privacy=yes)   
Mailing address: AuctionStealer Privacy Officer 8620 North New Braunfels, Suite 422 San Antonio, TX 78217
